{
    "subject": "Alan_Alda",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Four_Seasons__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Alda directed the film 'The Four Seasons'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8677754998207092,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Four Seasons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8137269020080566,
            "question": "Is Alan Alda known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7771139740943909,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Alan Alda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6613521575927734,
            "question": "What are some other films directed by Alan Alda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.606145977973938,
            "question": "When was the film 'The Four Seasons' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5164430141448975,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Four Seasons' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43532904982566833,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The Four Seasons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38820332288742065,
            "question": "Did the film 'The Four Seasons' receive positive reviews from critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3695397973060608,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors in 'The Four Seasons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21159885823726654,
            "question": "What awards did 'The Four Seasons' win or get nominated for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Alda directed the film 'The Four Seasons'.",
            "html": "yago_26396_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any famous actors in 'The Four Seasons'?",
            "html": "yago_26396_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did the film 'The Four Seasons' receive positive reviews from critics?",
            "html": "yago_26396_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The Four Seasons'?",
            "html": "yago_26396_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26396_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it is stated that \"Alan Alda's 1981 comedy drama film The Four Seasons is a lovely, heart-warming yarn of the joys and pains of three couples as they take holidays together over the four seasons.\" and \"The Four Seasons was written and directed by Alan Alda...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that Alan Alda is both the writer and director of the film \"The Four Seasons\" from 1981. Therefore, the statement that Alan Alda directed the film 'The Four Seasons' is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}